本作品之片源来自互联网，仅供学习、交流之用。请自觉于下载后24小时内删除。任何组织和个人不得用于任何商业用途，否则一切后果请自行承担！如果喜欢本片，请购买正版！
迪幻字幕组
为您奉献
很久以前  有一个女孩叫泰莎
Once upon a time, there was a girl named Tessa
灰 姑 娘 的 水 晶 鞋
她有一个梦想
who had a dream.
灰 姑 娘 的 水 晶 鞋
■
本字幕由★迪幻字幕组★为您奉献
欢迎登录 www.Deefun.com
迪幻
Deefun
欢迎关注迪幻微博 @迪幻Deefun
迪幻微信公众号 ideefun
整日忙碌  却一无所获
Workin' all day, don't do a thing
■
时间轴：PPMilkovich
其实你坐在驾驶座  可以掌控自己的生活
Life's what you make it, you're in the driver's seat
■
翻译：榴莲公主 关耳  Ennie
加大油门  拧动点火
Rev your engine, crank the ignition
■
翻译：zeroqian  PPMilkovich  洛洛落落
给我钥匙  你怎样都无法阻止我
Give me the key, don't need your permission
■
校订：PPMilkovich  洛洛落落
妈妈总是说
Momma always told me
■
后期：疲惫的皮蛋  黑潘
生活中没什么好怕的
There's nothin' in this life to fear
从懵懵懂懂到无所不能  你将会想念现在的我
You're gonna miss me zero to sixty
把生活拉回正轨
Kickin' it into gear
是我坐在驾驶座  掌控着生活
I'm in control and behind the wheel
想去哪里  就将一往无前
And I'm gonna steer where I want to steer
是我坐在驾驶座  掌控着生活
I'm in control and behind the wheel
想去哪里  就将一往无前
And I'm gonna steer where I'm gonna steer
加足马力
Go full throttle
全速前进
Pedal to the metal
没什么好怕的
Nothin' to fear
让自己进入正轨
Get yourself in gear
加足马力
And go full throttle
Go full throttle
松开离合  飞速前进
Pop out the clutch get this thing in drive
如果你不想成为匆匆过客
Don't want to be a passenger who's just cruisin' by
刮到保险杠  也没关系
Scratch the bumper it doesn't matter
但是这个故事  是关于她的现实生活
But this is a story about her reality.
泰莎  你最好快点  那个老巫婆刚到了
Better hurry, Tessa, the wicked witch just arrived.
泰莎
Tessa!
-泰莎  泰莎  泰莎  -没关系  这儿有我呢
- Tessa! Tessa! Tessa! - It's alright, I got this.
谢谢你  乔
Thanks, Joe.
她正度假  可能脾气会好点
Hey, maybe she gets nicer on vacation.
我的天哪  泰莎
Holy crapola, Tessa!
你把我最喜欢的包磨坏了
You scuffed my favorite bag.
对不起  迪万  要拿的东西太多了
I-I'm sorry, Divine,this is a lot to carry.
泰莎  我们可是一起拿呢
Well, we're all pitching in, Tessa.
我叫辆行李车
I'll ring the cart...
不要
No.
我才不会给这些贪婪的人小费呢
No way am I tipping those vultures.
不要  就不
No! No!
小心看着点闪闪
Be extra careful with Sparkles.
谁是好狗狗呀
Who's a good dog?
-谁是好狗狗  -迪万
- Who's a good dog? - Divine?
怎么了
What? Yes?
他已经死了
He's dead.
他还活在我心里呢  泰莎
Not in my heart, Tessa.
妈
Mom!
贵宾公主套餐还包括个化妆舞会
The VIP Princess package includes a costume party,
里德·韦斯特也会出席
and Reed West is performing!
让我看看
Let me see!
让一让
Over here. Must you...
更好的是  我们还有
Even better, we get our own private
七分钟和里德·韦斯特单独见面
7-minute Reed West encounter!
我们在里面可不能只待七分钟  雅典娜
We're in it for a lot more than seven minutes, Athena!
我们是冲着赢来的
We're here to win.
好  我马上就到
Okay, I'll-- I'll be there in a minute.
你会是 下一个
灰姑娘吗
周五试镜
有个游泳池  雅典娜  你要穿上比基尼
Oh, a pool. Athena, you need to put on your bikini
-坐在泳池边  -好的
- and sit by that pool. - Okay.
没说你  奥林匹亚
Uh, not you, Olympia.
我的天哪
Oh, my God.
这些女孩看着很专业啊
These girls look like pros.
她们身上可没流淌着
They don't have superstar's blood
巨星的血液
coursing through their veins.
记住  姑娘们  你们是麦当娜的第三代表亲
Remember, girls, you're Madonna's third cousins
隔了两辈
twice removed.
也没多少血缘关系
Not a lot of blood.
血缘就是血缘
Blood is blood.
如果我年轻10岁
If I were 10 years younger,
我就自己上了
I'd snag that role myself.
不好  珍妮特来了
Uh-oh, Janet's here.
她父母还让她去了纽约的音乐训练营
Her parents send her to music camp in New York.
姑娘们  贵宾午宴上见
See you ladies at the VIP lunch.
我都等不及了
Ah, can't wait!
碧安卡也在这儿
Bianca's here too!
劳伦
Lauren!
迪万
Divine!
你换了个脸
I almost didn't recognize you
我都差点没认出来你
with your new face.
你想要那儿的电话吗
Would you like the number?
他们也做抽脂
They do lipo as well.
我都忘了你有多诙谐了
I'd forgotten how dreadfully witty you are.
我们都很期待这个星期的活动
So we're really excited about this week.
对不对  碧安卡
Right, Bianca?
亲爱的  宝贝
Sweetheart? Darling?
碧安卡  亲爱的
Bianca, sweetheart.
是啊  太兴奋了
Yeah. So excited.
她是不是有点懒散啊
She's a bit of a slug, isn't she?
她一直在排练
She's been rehearsing.
你就带了一个助手
You've only brought one assistant.
真是勇敢
So brave.
我不是她助手
Oh, uh, I'm not her assistant,
我是她的继女
I'm her stepdaughter.
-泰莎  -什么
- Uhh, Tessa? - Yeah?
你能去把闪闪带过来吗
Could you please go get Sparkles?
-带闪闪来  -好  迪万  我马上去
- Get Sparkles! - Yes, right away, Divine.
谢谢你
Thank you.
她对于自己
She's a bit sensitive
在生活中的位置有点敏感
about her position in life.
跟你聊天很有意思
Well, it's been fascinating,
但是  现在我感觉无聊了
but, mm, now I'm bored.
泰莎  我们走
Tessa, we're on the move!
马上来
Right away!
里德
Oh, Reed,
为了你  我卖器官都行
I would sell body parts for you.
值钱的那些
Good ones.
真恶心  别流口水了  奥林匹亚
Ugh, gross. Stop drooling, Olympia.
为了他  卖个肾绝对值了
He's definitely worth a kidney.
他看起来有女朋友了  那个女孩是谁
He looks taken. Who's the girl?
哈珀·哈尔斯顿
Ugh. Harper Halston.
-是那个女继承人  -她可真漂亮
- The heiress. - She's so pretty.
皇家湖度假村是她家的
Her family owns Royal Lagoon Resorts.
这场海选由他们主办
They're holding the audition contest.
你要不是忙着给化油器抹油什么的
You'd know all this if you weren't so busy
你就知道了
greasing up carburetors or whatever.
你指我的工作
You mean my job.
泰莎  这个星期可不一样
Not this week, Tessa.
你来这里是要帮雅典娜和奥林匹亚
You're here to help Athena and Olympia
达成一个目标
focus on one thing,
那就是迷倒里德  当上主角
dazzling Reed and winning the lead role.
你们其中一个将在音乐剧中担任主演
One of you girls is going to star in the musical,
拿下唱片合约
win that recording contract,
让我骄傲
and do me proud.
我给你们起女神的名字是有原因的
I named you after goddesses for a reason.
什么音乐剧
What's the musical?
-《灰姑娘》  -《灰姑娘》
- Cinderella. - Cinderella.
好吧  还真有点讽刺
Okay, that's kind of ironic.
你  跟我来
You follow me.
是的  夫人
Yes, ma'am.
你会爱上你的小房间
You are going to love your little room.
就在这边
Okay, so it's right this way.
好的
Okay, all right.
就跟有你自己的私人温泉似的
It's just like having your own spa.
就在这后面
Right through here.
就是这儿
Here we go.
就在楼梯下  又漂亮又舒适
Nice and cozy, under the stairs.
所以说我是哈利·波特
So I'm Harry Potter.
没错
Exactly.
小心看着大门
Now, um, be careful of the gate,
门是从外面锁的
because it locks from the outside.
别告诉任何人你在这里  好吗
A-And don't tell anyone you're here, okay?
让你住这儿  我可要惹大麻烦了
Oh, I'm going to get into so much trouble for this.
别担心  这种事儿我也不会发动态的
Don't worry, it's not exactly something I'll Instagram.
也是
Yeah.
谢谢
Thanks.
奥林匹亚  别弄了
Olympia, stop that!
太恶心了  停下
That's disgusting! Stop it!
天哪  你干什么呢
Oh, my God, what are you doing?
住手  别吃那个
Stop it! Don't eat that!
我真想不到你这么让我丢脸
I cannot believe you're humiliating me this way!
天哪
Oh, dear.
-真的准备好了  -我觉得你胜券在握
-Like really ready. -I think you have this in the bag.
我从来没见过这么多呆滞的女孩
I've never seen such a dull group of girls.
-你还记得珍妮特吗  -记得 珍  你好
- You remember Janet? - Oh, yes, oh, Jane, hello.
-是珍妮特  -你掉了
- It's Janet. - Oh, you dropped some--
泰莎  泰莎
Tess-- Tess-- Ah!
泰莎
Ow. Tessa.
女士们
Ladies...
非常感谢
Thank you so much.
她有点迟钝
She's-- She's a little slow,
但你知道  她闻起来很香
but you know, she smells good,
所以我们把她留在身边
so we keep her around.
你太坏了
You're so bad!
欢迎光临  贵宾们
Welcome, VIPs.
就这么一眼看过去
You know, by the looks of this crowd,
我还以为VIP的意思是  非常漂亮的人
you'd think VIP stands for "very beautiful person."
那应该是VBP了
I guess that'd be V.B.P.
但是  感谢
But um, ah, thank you!
欢迎  我是弗雷迪·马克斯
Welcome, everyone! I'm Freddie Marks,
担任导演  还有你们都认识的
the director,and you all know, heh,
流行歌手  里德·韦斯特
pop sensation Reed West.
嗨  很高兴来到这里
Hi, it's lovely to be here.
我在油管上发现了里德
I discovered Reed on YouTube,
现在我希望能找到一个全新的明星
and now I'm hoping to find a brand new star
就在这儿  就在这间屋子里
right here in this very room.
哈珀和里德唱了一首浪漫的二重唱
Harper sang a romantic duet with Reed.
下一个会是你吗
Will you be next?
试镜将明天早上举行
Ah, now, auditions will be held tomorrow morning.
之后准备好的节目将在贵宾们留在这里的
and the show will premiere on the very last night
最后一个晚上首演
of your VIP stay,
所以对于那些通过试镜的人来说
so this is gonna be a fast-paced,
这将是一场快节奏  让人兴奋的冒险
exciting adventure for all those who make the cast,
尤其是那一位非常幸运的年轻女士
especially one very lucky young lady.
最好的部分是
And the best part?
如果我们的灰姑娘打动了斯里克轨道唱片公司的主管
If our Cinderella impresses the Slick Tracks record execs,
她当场就可以签约
she'll be signed on the spot.
没错  听着不错吧
Yeah, how about that?
好了  祝大家好运
All right, so good luck, everybody,
-明天早上见  -谢谢
- and we'll see you all in the morning. - Thank you.
再见
Cheers.
泰莎  醒醒
Earth to Tessa...
妈妈  妈妈
Mom? Mom?
救我  妈妈  我快要淹死了  我快要淹死了
Help. Mom, I'm drowning, I'm drowning!
-我的天  -救命
- Oh, my God. - Help!
抱歉  等一下
Sorry, give me one second.
好了  抓住这个
Okay, grab this.
她要淹死的时候太好笑了
She's so funny when she's drowning.
太棒了
It's so great.
轻点  泰莎
Gently, Tessa.
你能往我脸上抹点吗
Will you do my face?
我抹匀了吗
Am I getting it all?
还行  就是
Mm, yeah, just, um,
我感觉你漏了一块  就在那儿
I think you missed a spot, just right...
-这儿吗  -是  就那儿
- There? - Yeah, right there.
-没别的了吧  -没了
- Was that it?-  Oh, yeah.
我们可不想让你晒伤
We wouldn't want you to get sunburned.
好了  你现在可以走了
Okay, good, you can go now.
好的
Okay.
喷
Spit.
因为  我们都想要一个知心好友
'Cause we all want a friend To call our own
有时候  天会变得很冷
These days get Mighty cold sometime
每当这时  只需闭上眼睛
So I guess I'll just make this wish
许下心愿
And close my eyes
我向星星许愿
And I'm wishing up on a star
无论你在哪里我都会找到你
That I'll find you Wherever you are
我就是知道  那个特别的人
And I just know That special someone's
-一定就在某个地方  -很棒的歌  是吧
- Out there somewhere. - Great song, huh?
是呀  很好听
Heh. Yes, it's beautiful.
没有人想要孤身一人
Nobody ever wants To be alone
因为我们都想要一个朋友
'Cause we all want a friend
对了  我是乔治
Oh, I'm Georgie, by the way.
是这个节目的化妆师
I'm the makeup artist for the show.
我是泰莎  现在是个仆人  任人摆布
Uh, I'm Tessa, currently an indentured servant.
但你也会唱歌
But you sing too.
所以我想我会闭上双眼
So I guess I'll just make this wish
我听见你哼歌儿了
I heard you humming.
我不会
No, um...
我的意思是  是  我喜欢音乐和舞蹈
I mean, yeah, I love music and dance,
但是  那应该是另一种生活了
but, um, maybe in another life.
只可惜  我们只能活一次
Too bad we only get one.
我只知道那个特别的人
I just know The special someone's
一定在某个地方
Out there somewhere
很高兴见到你
Um, it was nice to meet you.
嘿  那是500cc的双缸车吗
Hey, is that a 500cc twin?
-1950年的  对吧  - 是  你说是就是吧
- 1950, right? - Yeah, if you say so.
-你能不能  -我们是舞台工作人员  不懂摩托车
-  Can you just--? Yeah, we're stagehands, not really bike people.
转  转  好的  转弯
Turn, turn. All right, turn.
天哪  这是蓝比尼最早的作品之一
Wow, that's one of Lambini's very first
真正的运动型双V引擎
real sporting V-twin engines.
她  她真漂亮
She's-- She's beautiful.
你知不知道
You have any idea
这个运动型的东西为什么发动不了
why one of these sporting things won't start?
这样吧  我非常愿意找出原因
You know what, I'd love to figure it out.
我可以借用一下吗
Hey, can I borrow those?
我的裤子
My pants?
是  你的工作服
Yeah, your overalls.
-可以  当然可以  -谢谢
- Yeah-- I mean, yeah. -Thanks.
好了吗
Yeah?
发动试试
Start 'er up.
太棒了
Hell yeah.
干得好  泰莎
Oh, nice work, Tessa.
他们修好了摩托
Oh, they got the bike started.
我要在那儿就好了  你可以送我
I wish I was there. You could give me a ride.
定位器刚刚关了
Uh, yeah, the alignment was just off.
两个气缸应该一起运行才对
The two cylinders kind of needed to run as one,
-但现在都好了  -好的  太厉害了
-but it's all good now. -All right, brilliant.
谢谢  伙计
Thanks, mate.
伙计
Mate.
小德德
Reedsy-boo...
我能讲完我的故事吗
Can I finish my story?
我和基姆和帕里斯一起吃午饭
I have lunch with Kim and Paris.
好  当然
Uh, yeah, sure, sure.
太谢谢你们了  弗雷迪会掩护你们的
Guys, thanks so much. Freddie'll cover you.
好的  愚蠢
Okay. Stupid.
不好
Oh, no.
我得走了  伙计们  等会儿见
Um, I gotta go, guys, but I'll see you later.
摩托有什么问题随时告诉我  好吗
Let me know how the bike goes, 'kay?
谢谢
Thanks.
有些日子  我工作很努力
Some days I've worked so hard,
身体酸痛
my body aches
就像一个老太婆那样
like that of an old woman.
我的脸上  全都是灰
My face is covered in... cinders.
我的脚
My feet--
毕加索  你能在线里面涂色吗
Hey, Picasso, can you color inside the lines?
稳点行吗
Could you hold still？
下一个是我
Me next!
好了  闪闪
All right, Sparkles,
有一个非常重要的问题  我需要你的建议
I need your opinion on a very important subject.
你觉得呢
What do you think?
糖果色
Candy Yum-yum?
还是橙红色
Or Lady Danger?
你个淘气鬼
Ah, you rascal, you.
好吧  那就橙红色
All right, Lady Danger it is.
泰莎  救救闪闪
Tessa! Save Sparkles!
闪闪溺水了
Sparkles is drowning!
她快要淹死了  她快要淹死了
She's drowning! She's drowning!
别用太多护理品  泰莎
Don't use too much product,Tessa.
要吹得蓬松  但又不能显得做作
Fluffy, but not pretentious.
我能要一份
Hi. Can I...?
-给你  -谢谢
- There you go. - Thank you.
泰莎  过来坐
Hey, Tessa, come on over.
艾迪
Eddie...
-我来帮你  -你们好
- Let me get this for you. - Hey, guys.
谢谢
Thank you very much.
天哪  他们真厉害
My God, they're amazing.
我想你应该听说过
I guess you would hear
最有才的人才能出现在这里
The best talent makes beds in hall's trash.
泰莎  一起来
Come on, Tessa.
-跳舞去  快来  -去吧去吧
- Let's go dance, come on. - Go! Go!
泰莎  不错啊
Wow, Tessa!
太厉害了 来   再给我们露一手
That's crazy, girl. Come on, show us some more moves.
让我们看看你的动作
Come on, show us your moves!
-到你了  乔琪  -别这样
- Now it's your turn, Georgie. - Don't do it.
用你的双脚起舞
Get up on your feet
沉醉在节奏中
And get down to the beat
来吧  让我们浸没在喧嚣中
Come on, let's live it loud
来吧来吧  就从现在开始
Come on Come on, come on now
穿好你的舞鞋
Put on your dancing shoes
我们别无所有
We got nothing to lose
冲破束缚  正是时机
Break all the locks Now's your chance
打破框架  挥舞双手
Get out of the box And wave your hands
每个人都要纵情起舞
Everybody's got to move
你为什么不跳  来吧  好吗
What's your excuse? Come on, do you
工作结束  理应放松
Time to play When work is through, yeah
别找借口了  来吧  好吗
There's no excuse Come on, do you
我们要抛却规则
We're shakin' off the rules
随心所欲
And makin' our own rules
冲破束缚  正是时机
Break all the locks Now's your chance
打破框架  挥舞双手
Get out of the box And wave your hands
每个人都要纵情起舞
Everybody's got to move
你为什么不跳  来吧  好吗
What's your excuse? Come on, do you
工作结束  理应放松
Time to play When work is through, yeah
你为什么不跳  来吧  好吗
What's your excuse? Come on, do you
来吧好吗
Everyone, do you
每个人都要纵情歌舞
Everybody, keep on dancing
来吧好吗
Everyone, do you
好吗
Do you
纵情歌舞
Keep on dancing
别找借口了  来吧  好吗
There's no excuse Come on, do you
来吧好吗
Hey, hey, hey Do you
好吗
Ha, do you
来吧  好吗  好吗
Come on, do you Do you
别找借口了  来吧  好吗
What's your excuse? Come on, do you
好吗
Do you
好吗  好吗
Do you, do you
别找借口了  来吧  好吗
There's no excuse Come on, do you, oh yeah
都给我回去工作  快走
Get back to work! Come on!
你为什么不参加音乐剧的试镜
Why are you not auditioning for the musical?
谢谢你  乔琪  但是我的继母
Thanks, Georgie, but my stepmother
永远都不会同意我去试镜的
would never ever allow me to audition.
我有个主意
That's it!
什么
What?
变装试镜
Audition in disguise.
我知道  我知道你很擅长
Okay, I'm sure-- I'm sure you're great with makeup
用刷子之类的化妆  但我觉得
and with brushes and stuff, but I doubt it could...
把嘴撅起来
Pout for me.
真要这样吗  我不太确定
I'm not so sure about this.
别说话
Shush, shush and shush.
好了  我们开始吧
Yeah, let's begin.
门未上锁  我们破门而入
Kick in the door no locks
趴在地上  我们不会报警
Get on the floor We no call the cops
女士们先生们  你们应该清楚
Ladies and gentlemen You should know
这是砸场子  我们要做主角
This is a stick-up We steal the show
曾经的表演者  快跑吧
Now run Tiggy run run Tiggy run run
听到动静就快跑吧
Hearing that bum bum When it come come
我们身上的光芒足以使灯光黯然失色
Lights in a bomb When we in the room
致命一击
Bull's-eye.
有人为钱而来
One for the money
我们却会让你失控
We gonna make you Lose control
乔琪  她是谁
Oh, hey, Georgie, who's your friend?
-咱俩认识啊  -她是位客人  艾迪
- You know who I am. - She's a guest, Eddie.
是位客人
She's a guest.
如果你需要什么  只管吩咐我们
If you need anything, you just, you let us know.
我可以帮你  帮你打扫房间
I can sweep. Sweep your room.
打扫  打扫房间
Sweep, sweep rooms.
我还穿过他的工作服呢  他都没认出我
He didn't recognize me and I've worn his coveralls.
好吧  我不知道你在说什么
Okay, I don't know what that means,
但我确定了一点  你一定得去试镜
but I feel vindicated. Now you have to audition.
乔琪  听着  你的化妆刷
Georgie, look, your makeup brushes
就像魔杖一样神奇  但我不能去试镜
are like magic wands, but I can't do this.
我的家人一下子就会认出我的声音
My family will recognize my voice immediately.
那就伪装一下  我们到了
Then disguise it. Here we are.
不应该是
It's not like,
我是奥林匹亚
"I'm Olympia."
我在这里
"I'm here."
我是你的
"I'm yours."
好吧  我要过去了
Okay, I'm going.
好
Okay.
-我真的要去了  -好的  去吧
- I'm gonna do this. - Okay, go.
好的  我这就要去了
Okay, I'm gonna go.
-去吧  -好
- Just go.- Okay.
你根本没在听我说话
You're not listening to me.
珍妮特  你看起来不错
Wow, Janet, you look great.
别担心  别人根本不会注意到
And don't worry, no one will even notice
你额头涨出的青筋
that huge vein bulging out of your forehead.
年轻人  你是VIP客人吗
Young lady, are you a VIP guest?
我没在吃早午餐的时候看到过你
I didn't see you at the brunch.
电车坏了
Um, the trolley broke.
电车
The trolley?
是的  很遗憾电车坏了
Yes. But it's a bloody shame the trolley broke.
我肯定在哪儿见过你
I know you from somewhere.
不可能
No, um...
我没
Uh, I don't--
我觉得不可能
I don't think so.
在尼德迈耶  犹太少年成人礼上见过吗
The Niedermeyer Bar Mitzvah?
一起听过犹太歌
Did we Hava Nagila?
女士  我未曾有此殊荣
I don't think I had that pleasure, ma'am.
你确实没这等福分
Eh. You didn't have that pleasure.
那就是在费城的国际狗狗展示会上
The National Dog Show in Philly?
恐怕不是  我喜欢猫
Afraid not. Um, I'm a cat person.
-甚至你身上的味道我都觉得熟悉  -是香草味
- You even smell familiar. - It's vanilla.
是我体香剂的味道  这种味道在伦敦特别流行
It's my deodorant. It's all the rage in London.
英格兰
England.
很有意思
Very interesting.
行吧
All right.
好的
Yes.
我盯上你了
I've got my eyes on you.
没有必要  随便你
Oh, that won't be necessary, it's okay.
再见
Cheers!
天佑女王 远在伦敦的女王陛下
God save the queen. In London.
就是我家乡的那个伦敦
Where I'm from.
随便吧  奥林匹亚
Whatever. All right, Olympia...
太险了
Oh, that was close.
我知道大雨即将落下
I know the rain is falling
不必满面愁容
Don't look so sad about it
我知道也许会有点痛
I know it hurts a little
你想要高声呼喊
You want to scream And shout it
我有挽救方法
I got the remedy
就跟着节奏一遍一遍尽情摇摆
So let the rhythm take you Over and over
结尾会特别精彩
She has a big finish!
我知道你万分沮丧
I know you're down
我来让你展开笑颜
Let me picking you up
我知道你很坚强
I know you're strong
我知道你很坚韧
I know you're tough
你想坐在一旁
You want to sit
但你需要舞动
You need to move
就到这里吧  谢谢你
Okay, thank you, dear. Next!
请大点声
A little louder, please.
下一位
Next!
见证奇迹的时刻到了
Prepare to be amazed.
我说我们出发吧  我将带你前往巅峰
I said let's go, go Take it to the top now
我们态度强硬  永不止步
Goin' hard and we're Never gonna stop now
想象出我们和谐而又都在闪耀的图景
Picture us All a-rhyme and glow
但我们一刻都不能等了
But we cannot wait a second Baby no
所以我穿着细高跟  穿上脐装
So walkin' in stilettos In my midriff, midriff
操纵变速杆  全速前进
Pedal to the metal in My stick shift, stick shift
拼尽全力  吸引所有人的目光
Sit and rob attention,like you on a mission
是时候实现一些我清单上的愿望了
About to check Some shit off my wish list
我要开始了  没人能阻挡我
Gonna set it up And no one can stop me
我要开始了  等着瞧吧
I'm gonna turn it up Go ahead and watch me
停  停  快停下来
Stop! Stop! Stop! Stop!
放在那里就行了  别的搬走
Yeah, get right up there. Clear it out.
这就很完美了  这里要打光
That'll look perfect. There should be lighting right there.
开始吧
Okay, go ahead.
你们喜欢听什么
What's doth ye lads fancy?
我们想听什么   弗雷迪
What do we doth fancy, Freddie?
亲爱的  你来之前应该有所准备
You're supposed to come prepared, sweetie.
是的
Right.
我只是  等一下
I just-- Just one second.
没有人愿意孤身一人
Nobody ever Wants to be alone
因为我们都想要一个知心好友
'Cause we all want a friend To call our own
有时候  天会变得很冷
These days get mighty cold Sometimes
每当这时  只需闭上眼睛  许下心愿
So I guess I'll just make This wish and close my eyes
这世上没有我不能涉足之处
There is no place That I won't go
为了寻求真爱  我愿上刀山
Because for love I will search high
也愿下火海
And I'll search low
不论付出什么代价  我愿意一试
All things worth having Takes a risk
只要有机会
If I got one shot
希望我不会错过
I hope that I don't miss
我对着星星许愿
And I'm wishin' Upon a star
无论你在世界上的哪个角落  我都会找到你
That I'll find you Wherever you are
我知道  属于我的那个他就在某个地方
And I just know that special Someone's out there somewhere
很普通
Well, it's pretty average.
你叫什么名字
What's your name?
-灰姑娘  -灰姑娘
- Um, Cinderella. - Cinderella.
挺讽刺
Oh. Ironic.
一点点
Just a bit.
我喜欢你的上衣
I like your top.
我有一条图案一样的短裤
I've got a pair of boxers like those.
伦敦万岁
Go London.
-爱国主义  你懂的  -懂
- Patriotic, you know. - Yeah, heh.
你到底是哪里人
Where about you from?
我有点辨别不出你的口音
I can't quite find your accent.
你听不出来吗
Oh, you can't?
真奇怪
That's odd.
我是从  一个小村庄来的
I'm from-- It's a small farming village.
在伦敦北部
It's just north of London.
名字是
It's called, um...
约克郡布丁县
It's called Yorkshire Puddingshire.
-约克布丁郡  -约克郡布丁县
York Puddingshire? York-- Yorkshire.
约克郡布丁县  这样啊
Yorkshire Puddingshire, oh.
-是的  -好吧
- Yes - Okay.
是挨着
Oh, is that near...?
没错
Y-- Uh-huh.
就在
It's-- It's right--
就在霍格沃茨郡边上
It's right near Ho-- Hogwarts shire.
-霍格沃茨郡  弗莱迪  -是的
- Hogwarts shire, Freddie. - Yes.
我就知道
I knew it.
好吧
Yeah. Okay.
约克郡布丁县女孩  让我看看你跳舞跳得怎么样
Well, Yorkshire Puddingshire, let me see if you can move.
你想让我跳舞
You want me to dance?
是的  我非常想看你跳舞
Yeah, I'd love you to dance.
告诉我  你喜欢我的舞步吗
Tell me, baby Did you like the way I move?
换上你的舞鞋
Come on, Get your dancer on
你能尽享欢乐
You can have as much fun As you can possibly have
别忘了穿裤子
With your pants on
当我望进你的双眼
When I look in your eyes
他们告诉我  冷静
They saying chillax
我肯定  有个魔鬼住在那里
I bet you There's a devil inside
我们彼此相连
Hookin' and playin', baby
我不想失控
I hate to lose
所以在舞池中展示给我看吧
So show me On the dance floor
我看得出你很在行
I can see you got game
我也是行家
Well, I got game
你最好给我一手  来吧
You better show me By your game, come on
让我们开始吧
Let's get this game on
来吧  宝贝
Come on, babe
让我们开始吧
Let's get this game on
是谁点燃了爱的火花
Who can start a fire?
就是这样的火花
The fire be like that
你准备好了吗  准备好什么
Are you ready? For what?
-你会跳萨尔萨舞吗  -一点都不会
- Can you salsa? Oh. - Not at all.
-接住我  -接住你
- Catch me. - Catch you?
游戏人间嘛  你懂的  这没关系
Everything is playing You know, it's all right
如果咱们只是玩玩
If you're playing With me now, oh yeah
-她是谁  -不好说
- Who the hell is she? - Uh, it's hard to say.
为什么她有跳舞的机会
Why does she get to dance?
不好说  她是个冒牌货
Hard to say? She's an imposter!
她都没出席早午餐聚会
She wasn't even at the kickoff brunch!
她现在出现了啊
Well, she's here now.
很抱歉  我得走了
I'm so sorry, I have to go.
什么  不  等一下  你很厉害  等一下
What? No, wait, you're amazing. Wait.
抓住她  她冒充VIP
Arrest that girl! She's impersonating a VIP!
抓住那个女孩
Arrest that girl!
我猜大概童话大神显灵了
Well, I guess the fairy tale gods have spoken.
你们俩一起跳舞的时候
The way you two danced together...
就像童话成真了
It was like a fairy tale.
我肯定  他会选你
I bet he's gonna pick you.
这不重要了  你看到我继母的嘴脸了
It doesn't matter. You saw Divine.
她能分分钟让我失去资格
She'd get me disqualified in a heartbeat.
我们会想出一个假名字  一切都会很顺利的
We'll come up with a fake name and it'll all work out.
乔琪  我很抱歉
Georgie, I'm really sorry.
我真的  很感激你
I really-- I really appreciate everything
感激你为我所做的一切  但是
you've done for me, but...
我觉得是时候回到现实了
I think it's time for me to get back to my real life.
但还是谢谢你
But thank you.
坐直了  坐直了
Oh-oh, sit up straight. Sit up straight.
我想
Well, I'd just like to start off by saying
向大家道谢开始
thank you very much to everyone here
谢谢你们参加今天的试镜
for auditioning today.
我们即将张贴配角名单
We're posting a cast list soon of the secondary roles,
但是
but...
我找到我的灰姑娘了
I found my Cinderella.
现在我只需要在人群中真的找出她
Well, now I just need to actually find her, heh.
这位神秘的灰姑娘
Our mystery Cinderella,
她今天在试镜的时候遗失了一只舞鞋
she lost her dance shoe today at the audition.
是一只很特别的鞋子
It's a very special shoe.
如果你有与之配对的鞋
Uh, if you're the owner of that matching shoe,
请在明天午夜前来找我
then please come forward by midnight tomorrow...
这个角色就是你的了
and the role is yours.
谢谢大家
Thank you.
姑娘们  姑娘们  让开  别挡路
Girls! Girls! Out of my way! Out of my way!
跟我走  跟上跟上
Excuse me! Follow me! Try to keep up! Try to keep up!
都让开  我要过来了
Clear the road! Coming through!
-这个吗  -不是
- This one? - Nope.
-这个呢  这个呢  -不是  还不是
- This one? This one? - Nope. Nope.
-是这个吗  -不是
- This one? - Nope.
-这个呢  -我不确定
- This one? - I'm not sure!
使劲想  奥林匹亚
Think, Olympia.
调动起你那所剩不多的脑细胞
Round up every last little brain cell that's in there.
早上好
Good morning.
-这个吗  这个呢  -不是  也不是
This one? This one? Nope. Nope.
这个  等等  就是它
This-- Wait. Yes.
这个  这个就是那个鞋花  就是那个
That's-- That's the shoe flower, that's the one.
泰莎
Oh. Tessa...
你得把这朵花画在这个鞋子上
You need to paint that flower on this shoe.
没什么意义吧
Um, there's no point,
因为如果他有相对应的另一只运动鞋  那么
because if he has the matching sneaker, then--
其他人都不知道这个手绘花
Nobody else knows about the hand-painted flower.
他必须在午夜前挑选一个人
He has to pick somebody by midnight.
去  去  去
Go! Go! Go!
你猜怎么着  《放松》刚刚进了公告牌排行榜最热100
Guess what? "Get Loose" just made the Billboard Hot 100!
这也太快了
Wow, that was fast.
看  我告诉过你  和哈珀合作二重唱会给你的事业镶金的
See, I told you duet with Harper would be gold for your career.
如果有人感兴趣
Uh, if anybody's interested,
配角选角名单刚刚张贴在后台了
the supporting cast list has just been posted backstage.
来吧  里德  我们走吧
Come on, Reed, let's go!
好吧  我尽力了  但我真的不认为这会有效果
Okay, I tried, but I just really don't think this is gonna work.
怎么了  是有人死了吗
What happened? Did someone die?
比这更糟  碧安卡要扮演仙女教母
Worse! Bianca got cast as Fairy Godmother.
珍妮特扮演恶毒的继母
Janet's the Evil Stepmother,
而我们要演的却是
and all we get to play is the...
丑陋的继姐  丑陋的继姐
Ugly Stepsisters! Ugly Stepsisters!
他们怎么可以认为  我们应该饰演
How could they possibly think that we should play
那种卑鄙  又超级自私的女孩
those mean, horrible self-absorbed girls?!
天啊  这简直符合想象  不是吗
Gosh, it just boggles the imagination, doesn't it?
终于搞定了
Finally.
什么  你是用脚趾头画的吗
What, did you paint it with your toes?
像往常一样  我会处理好一切的
As usual, I'll take care of things.
对吗  姑娘们
Right, girls?
你没听见吗
Uh, hello?
门铃响了
Doorbell.
奥林匹亚  坐直
Olympia, sit up straight.
雅典娜  别摆出一副沮丧的表情
Athena, stop looking so depressed.
信是里德·韦斯特的
It's from Reed West.
里德·韦斯特希望陪同见面的人有
"Reed West requests the company of..."
不
No!
他写了什么  发生什么了
What is it? What's wrong?
你
You!
他为什么想见你
Why does he want to see you?!
什么
What?
我看见你在里德说话的时候
I saw you at Reed's announcement
眼睛都黏在他身上了
making gooey eyes at him.
不  这  这太荒
No, it's-- That's ridic--
你为了他去修眉毛了  是不是
You plucked your eyebrows for him, didn't you?
不  我没有  我没有  只是
No, I didn't, I didn't. It's just--
这只是一些  一个大误会
It's just some-- A big misunderstanding.
这只是个愚蠢的错误  这样  我们会弄明白的  好吗
It's just a silly mistake. Well, we'll find out, shall we?
跟我来
Come with me!
姑娘们  姑娘们  我们要走了
Girls! Girls! We're leaving!
看这里  凝视这里
See there, staring here
是的  我们要搞清楚这件事的真相
Yeah, we're gonna get to the bottom of this
现在  小姑娘  如果你把我家女孩们的事搞砸了
right now, little missy, and if you screw things up for my girls--
姑娘们  快点跟上
Girls, try to keep up.
里德  里德·韦斯特
Oh, Reed. Reed West.
我把泰莎带来了  你想见她吗
I have Tessa here. You wanted to see her?
等一下
Oh, hang on a sec.
是的  我们一直在找你
Oh, yes, we've been trying to track you down.
你在找我
You have?
你为什么想要想见她
Uh, why would you want to see her?
我  我只是需要你的帮助
Well, I-- I just need your help.
-是吗  -演出差不多就要靠它了
- You do? - The show kinda depends on it.
是吗
It does?
机修工说
The mechanic said
昨天是你发动了摩托车
you were the one who got her started yesterday.
对  对  是我
Yeah. Yeah. I did.
很抱歉  误认为你是个男生
I'm sorry for mistaking you for a dude.
我的错
It's my bad.
没关系  我只是
It's okay, I'm just--
我很高兴现在一切都明了了
I'm just glad everything's all cleared up now.
好吧  还有一个问题
Right, well, there's a--
车一直发出一种轻微的噪声
There's like a little clunking noise
声音是从  从
coming from the-- From, uh--
摩托车上发出来的
Uh, from the motorcycle.
-摩托的声音  -对
- From the bike. - Yeah.
你能描述一下吗
Um, could you describe the clunking?
知道了  是那种快速的突突声吗
Okay. Is it like a fast tk-tk?
有点像  它开始是像
Kind of. Well, it starts off--
感觉声音不断增强
It starts off like it's building.
好，那就是
Okay. So like "b-b-b-b-b" tk, tk?
不  更像
No, it's more like
像火车一样
Like a train?
我不知道那是什么火车  但是  是这样的
I don't know what trains you've heard, but yeah,
关掉就没声儿了  如果我试着再发动
it cuts out, and if I try and do it again,
它就继续  突  突  突  突  突
it goes, tk, tk, tk, tk, tk, tk.
好了  我知道问题在哪儿了
Um, yeah, I think I know it.
好吧  能修好就修好
Well, we just need to get it fixed if we can,
不然的话灰姑娘就没有南瓜车了
otherwise Cinderella won't have a pumpkin carriage.
我可以试试
I can try.
等等  等等  等等  等等
Wait, wait, wait, wait.
如果我让我亲爱的泰莎为你做这件事
If I let my darling Tessa do this for you,
你必须为我做点什么
you have to do something for me.
你必须让我富有才华的女儿们再次试镜
You have to let my talented daughters audition again.
她们第一次试镜遇到了些小问题
They had an eentsy problem the first time.
顺便说一句
By the way,
准备好  她们会惊艳到你的
prepare to have your mind blown.
好  成交
Yeah, deal.
来吧  姑娘们  我们要去练习了
Come on, girls, we have to practice!
再见
Bye.
弗雷迪  我们能带泰莎去道具间吗
Uh, Freddie, can we set Tessa up in the prop room, please?
不是
It's not--
我发誓  没看上去的那么糟
It's not as bad as it looks, I swear, heh.
跟我刚才看到的混乱一比  不值一提
Well, this is nothing compared to the hot mess I just saw, heh.
当然  我不小心听到了一点
I'm sure, I kind of overheard a little bit.
好的  这些是我需要你拿来的部件
Okay, so these are the parts that I need you to get,
这样我就可以修好你的南瓜车了
so that I can fix your pumpkin carriage.
你是从哪里学会做这些的
Where did you learn to do all this?
我爸爸是赛车手
Um, my dad was a racecar driver.
是啊
Yeah.
他有自己的修理店
He had his own repair shop,
所以基本上是
so I was basically
在我能走路之前  就和车打交道
working on cars before I could walk.
你爸爸现在还赛车吗
Is your dad still racing cars now?
要是这样就好了
Um, I hope so.
他去世了
In heaven.
你能把9/16英寸扳手递给我吗
Could you pass me the 9/16th spanner?
-不能  -就是扳钳
- No. - Oh, the wrench.
不  我不知道是哪一个
No, I don't know what that one is.
那个小的  银色的
The small, silver thing, r--
-是这个  -对
-This one? -Mm-hm.
这个小的银色工具  就是这个
Small silver thing here. Right there.
-你刚开始就该这么说  -谢谢
- You should've just said that. - Thanks, heh.
你爸爸也让小泰莎驾驶赛车吗
So did your dad let Baby Tessa drive racecars too?
没有
No.
没有  我到5岁才能开
No, I had to wait till I was about 5 for that.
好吧  非常明智
Ha, ha. All right, wise to wait.
你做到了  宝贝
You did it, babe!
演出门票售罄了  度假区也是
The show sold out. The resort too.
-爸爸高兴极了  -  太好了
- Heh, Dad's thrilled. - Oh, that's great.
弗雷迪说你还没有选好女主角
Freddie says you haven't cast Cinderella yet?
是啊  还没有
No, not yet.
但是我们已经有了能接下角色的人选
But there's someone we're hoping's gonna accept it.
那就加油啊  大帅哥
Then make it happen, hot stuff.
好了  我要起飞了
Anyway, gotta fly.
发生了很多事
a lot goin' on.
没关系
It's okay.
如果这个女孩再不出现  我就有麻烦了
I'm in trouble if this girl doesn't show.
你真的认为你的神秘女孩那么好吗
You really think your mystery girl's that good?
那当然
Oh, definitely.
但皇家度假区希望我们今天就能完成选角
But Royal Resorts want us to complete casting today.
如果神秘女孩不站出来
And if mystery girl doesn't come forward,
我们也必须挑选其他人
then we have to pick someone else.
我喜欢和你一起待着
I like spending time with you.
如果你明天能见我  我也会很高兴的
I'd really like it if you'd meet me tomorrow,
还有  也许
and maybe, uh,
我能拿着你的扳钳
well, you'd let me hold your spanner.
我的天哪
Oh, my God.
我以为他是那种
I thought he was going to be like,
身材很好  人很狂妄的类型  但是
all abs and attitude, but...
他  他真是太贴心了
he's-- He's so sweet.
这里有人坠入爱河了
Heh, someone's crushing hard.
算了吧  他在和一位漂亮又有名的女继承人约会
Oh, please, he's dating a gorgeous celebrity heiress.
她连给你提鞋的资格都没有
Who can't possibly hold a candle to you.
她不需要这样做  有人会帮她做
She doesn't have to, she has people for that.
没关系  事情本来就是这样
It's okay, it's just the way things are.
我希望
I wish...
什么
What?
你爸爸
Your dad.
他实现了他的梦想  对吧
He made his dreams come true, right?
是啊
Yeah.
他应该也希望你实现梦想吧
Wouldn't he want you to do the same?
我只是不想看到
I just hate to see
完美的梦想被白白浪费
perfectly good dreams go to waste.
好了  爸爸
Okay, Dad,
我会勇敢起来
I'll be brave.
快来
Come on!
需要花多长时间
How much longer is this gonna take?
我不知道
I don't know.
-我不知道  -好的
- I don't know. - All right.
看  她不来了  我们可以再选一个人了吗
Look, she's not coming. Can we just pick someone?
不  还没到午夜
No, it's not midnight yet.
再等几分钟
Just a few more minutes.
停下
Stop it!
太烦人了
So annoying.
真是服了
Unbelievable.
里德  如果我们再不挑人
Reed, if we don't pick someone,
他们会取消我们的演出
they'll cancel my show.
拜托了
Please?
好吧
All right.
我来得太晚了吗
Am I too late?
-就是她  对吧  -是
- It's her, right? - Heh, yeah.
-你好  -你好
- Hello.  -Hello.
樱花是我妈妈最喜欢的花
Cherry blossoms were me mum's favorite flowers.
你为什么跑了
Why did you run?
我很犹豫到底要不要来试镜
I wasn't sure I should've auditioned at all.
哦
Oh.
那你改变主意了吗
Well, you've changed your mind?
你要当我的灰姑娘吗
All right, you'll be my Cinderella?
嗯
Yes.
等一下
Hold on a second!
等一等
Wait one minute!
等等  等等  我有话要说
Hold on! Hold on! I have something to say!
这个女孩
This girl,
我敢打赌她不是一名合法的客人
I bet she's not even a legitimate guest.
什么  那太荒谬了
What? That's absurd.
哦  太荒谬了
Oh, absurd!
你叫什么名字
Well, what's your name?
我的名字
My name?
没错
Hm, yes.
对啊  因为每个人
Right, because everyone--
每个人都有名字  对吧
Everyone has a name, right?
快说
Spit it out.
名字
The-- See, the name
我妈妈给我起的名字是
that my mother gave me was...
贝拉
Bella!
Bella.
-贝拉·贝金汉姆  -贝拉·斯诺
- Bella Buckingham. - Bella Snow!
- Bella Buckingham？  - Bella Snow！
是贝拉·贝金汉姆·斯诺
It's Bella Buckingham Snow.
简称贝拉·斯诺
Bel-- Bella Snow, for short.
很高兴见到你
It's good to see you!
我刚才还去了你妈妈的城堡
I was just at your mom's castle.
在  在约克郡布丁县  多可爱啊
In-in Yorkshire Puddingshire, how lovely, heh!
是的  贝拉·斯诺  会员  她是合法的
Yep, Bella Snow, VIP. She's legit.
好的  好的  好的
Okay, all right. All right.
我盯上你了
I'm on to you!
你和你的蠢运动鞋
You and your silly sneakers
最好都小心点
had better watch your step!
好了  看剧本
Okay then, read this,
检查各项环节  熟悉作息安排
check out the links, learn the routines,
早上开始排练
start rehearsal in the morning.
好的
All right, heh.
迪幻
Deefun
不行  你不能喝碳酸饮料
No! No carbs for you!
你太胖了
You're getting too fat.
这是你要的平板电脑
Here's the tablet you requested.
好的  坐下  我想让你搜点东西
All right. Sit down, I want you to Google something.
好   你想让我搜什么
Okay, what do you want me to Google?
搜一下  "贝拉·斯诺"
Google "Bella Snow."
-斯诺  -贝拉·斯诺
- Snow. - Bella Snow.
斯诺[雪]  就是会从天上飘下来的东西
Snow, like the stuff that falls from the sky.
B-E-L-  电脑给我
B-E-L-- Just give that to me.
让我来搜  你太慢了
Let me do it. You're so slow.
你来搜  她太慢了
You do it. She's too slow.
好了
Okay...
好了  这里有一个
Okay, here's one.
贝拉·斯诺
Bella Snow,
一名新泽西的牙科医生
a dentist in New Jersey.
那不是她
That's not her.
那个女孩可没那么聪明
That girl is as brainless as they come.
好吧  我找到一个英国人叫贝拉·斯诺
Okay, I found a British Bella Snow,
她一百年前就去世了
who died a hundred years ago.
没用的  她根本就不存在
This is pointless. She doesn't exist!
我就知道  她是个冒牌货
I knew it! She's an imposter!
我要你在排练结束后跟着她
I want you to follow her after rehearsal,
弄清楚她是谁
and find out who she is.
我
Me?
-我也要去  -我可以去吗
- I will go, too.  - Can I go?
嘘  嘘
Shh! Shh!
嘘
Shh!
我去确认一下厨师是否清楚
I'm gonna go make sure the chef
你们的晚餐要求
has your suggestions for dinner.
好吧  我跟你说
Oh, all right. And you know,
我今天想坐在小屋旁的喷雾站
I want the spritzing station by the cabana today.
-知道了  -我喜欢喷雾的感觉
-Got it. -I love to be spritzed.
到时候就跟着你的感觉走
Just go with what you're feeling at the time.
不要事先计划好
And don't decide beforehand.
就跟着那一瞬间的感觉走  好吗
Just let it be whatever you're feeling in the moment, okay?
-可以吗  -好
- Yeah? - Cool.
太好了  你来了
Oh, good, you're here.
好了  我们想来一首灰姑娘的开场曲
Okay, so, um, we wanna do Cinderella's opening song.
你准备好了  对吧
You're ready, right?
好的  各位  让我们给她留一些空间
Okay, great, let's give her some space, folks.
这首歌讲述的是一个生活艰难的女孩
Right, the song's about a girl who lives a difficult life,
她总是失败
filled with loss,
难以找寻勇气去追逐她的梦想
who struggles to find the courage to go after her dreams.
试着去体会一下那种感觉  好吗
Try to imagine what that might be like, okay?
我会的
I can try.
好了  大家各就各位
Okay, places, everybody.
我是这样一个人
I've never been one
不曾踏出自己的舒适圈
To step out of My comfort zone
每次努力时
Whenever I try
都担心自己止步不前
I'm afraid to just let go
我是这样一个人
I've never been one
不曾挣脱束缚自由翱翔
To break free
因为我总是在意他人的目光
'Cause I've always cared What everyone thinks Of me
我不知道我为什么逃跑
Don't know why I run
我不知道我为什么隐藏
Don't know why I hide
不让他人知晓自己真实的内心
Never let them know What I feel inside
我不知道我为什么害怕
Don't know why I'm scared
当我站立于此
Just to take a chance
只能放手一搏
When I'm just standing here
如同飞鸟  我自由飞翔
Like a bird I'm free to fly
张开双翼  寻找生命的意义
Spread my wings And find my life
如同飞鸟  我飞入高空
Like a bird I'm up so high
飞出牢笼  是时候大放异彩
Out of the cage It's my time to shine
如同飞鸟  我自由飞翔
Like a bird I'm free to fly
所以告诉我  告诉我
So tell me, tell me
我为什么要逃避
Why don't I?
我们终于找到合适的女主了
We definitely found our girl.
好了
Okay.
举起手臂  向上  向上  向上
Arms up. Up, up, up.
抱歉
Sorry.
你的腰细得就跟小蜂鸟一样
You got a waist like a little hummingbird.
再见
Cheers.
贝拉
Bella.
乔吉
Georgie.
看看你  跟公主一样
Oh, look at you, all princessy!
我第一次觉得
For the first time, I feel like...
也许我能做到  真的能做到
maybe I can do this. Like, for real.
你好
Hi!
-过来  -天啊
- Come on! - Ugh, my God,
我的姐姐们就在外面等着我
my stepsisters are waiting to follow me outside.
我们从后面走  她们不会想到的
We'll go out the back. They won't expect it.
-你确定吗  -那当然了
- You sure? - Mm-hm.
好吧  那我走了  拜
Okay. I'm gonna go. Bye. Okay.
她去哪里了
Where is she?
快跟上
Come on!
知道了
Okay.
-好吧  你走那边  -好
- Okay. You go that way. - Okay.
抓到你了
Catch you.
干嘛
What?
你是谁
Who are you?
-抓到你了  -奥林匹亚
- Catch you. - Olympia!
在  在这里见到你真是太高兴了
Oh, it's just such a-- Such a delight to see you here.
是吗
It is?
你能不能
Would you be so kind as to
把防晒霜递给我
pass me that suntan lotion over there too?
我们英国人  可禁不起晒
We Brits, we just crisp so easily.
能帮我下吗  我够不着
Oh, do you mind? I can't reach.
谢谢你
Thank you.
跟我说说吧  奥林匹亚
So tell me, Olympia,
把这些围巾都塞进嘴里是不是很困难
was it hard to get all those scarves in your mouth?
哦  我已经训练好几个星期了
Oh, I had to train my cheeks for weeks.
-是吗  -你想看看吗
- Did you? - Do you wanna see?
当然
Sure.
塞了好多葡萄啊
That's a lot of grapes.
你知道怎么样才能显得更可爱吗  加一些柠檬水
Do you know what would be lovely? Some lemonade.
再加点零食
Mm. And snacks.
-是的  还有零食  -我去拿
- Yes, and snacks. - I can get 'em!
-哦  你去吧  -嗯哼
- Oh, you could. - Mm-hm.
-那实在是太好了  -好的
- Oh, that's absolutely perfect. - Okay.
谢谢  我就在这里等你
Thank you. I'll be just right here waiting,
就在这里  不会走的
right here, won't move.
她人很好  又聪明
She's so nice. And smart.
只是在我帮她拿来零食之前
Oh. But then she disappeared
她就消失了
before I could give her her snacks.
你被耍了  奥林匹亚
Ugh. You got played, Olympia.
你就是嫉妒
You're just jealous
因为贝拉比你更漂亮
because Bella's head is prettier than yours.
你去哪里了
Where have you been?
我刚去拿你们订的衣服了
I was just picking up the dresses you ordered.
这是为化妆舞会准备的吗
Are these for the Costume Ball?
我们要打扮成灰姑娘
We're going as Cinderellas.
嘛哩嘛哩哄
Abracadabra!
哈哈哈  那个  魔法师就是这么说的
Heh, heh, just... that's what a magician says.
这是你的魔杖
Uh, so this is your wand.
用法很简单  我给你演示一下
It's very simple to use. Just demonstrate for you.
基诺  你能站到灰姑娘的位置上吗
Uh, Gino, could you step into Cinderella's position, please?
-好的  -你只需要这样
- Yeah. - So all you do is...
转圈
twirl.
明白了吗
See?
很简单的  只需要转动手腕
Uh, it's so easy. Just a flick of the wrist.
拿好了  去感受下吧
Here, go ahead. Get a feel for it,
有任何问题  都可以跟我说
and, uh, let me know if you have any questions.
打扰一下
Sorry.
她太荒谬了吧
She's ridiculous.
你是怎么想的  居然让碧安卡和她的姐妹们出演
What were you thinking getting Bianca and her stepsisters in the show?
奥林匹亚  快住手  太恶心了
Olympia, stop it. Gross.
我们别无选择
We have no choice.
会员套餐承诺她们可以出演配角
The VIP package guarantees them supporting roles.
别担心了
Don't worry.
没事的
It'll be fine.
我能让每个人都有精彩的表现
I can get a great performance out of anybody.
这些翅膀太重了
These wings are so heavy.
她能演好的
She's gonna be great.
臂部有四个节拍
So it's four beats in the hips.
贝拉来了
Oh, uh, Bella's here,
那么  我们来排练下穿鞋的戏吧
so let's rehearse the shoe-fitting scene, please.
这就是接下来的安排
Yes, that's what we're gonna do.
弗雷迪
Freddie,
你能在没有我的情况下先排练吗
can you run the show without me for a little bit?
啥  为什么  你要去哪里
What? Why? Where are you going?
修理灰姑娘的南瓜马车
To fix Cinderella's pumpkin carriage.
没有它就没法演出了  对吧
Can't do the show without it, right?
我应该可以替你
I guess I'll stand in.
如果泰莎不在那里
If Tessa's not there,
他会觉得她是个骗子或者根本就没放在心上
he'll think she's a flake or doesn't care.
你没法同时出现在两个地方
You can't be in two places at once.
-带上工作服和帽子在化妆室等我  可以吗  -好
- Meet me in Make-up with coveralls and a cap, okay? - Okay.
-你要怎么办  -问得好
- How are you gonna pull this off? - Great question.
我先让里德开始  接着跟他说我要走了
I think I'll get Reed started, then tell him I have to go.
再回来这里和你碰面  戴上贝拉的假发
I'll just meet you back here for the Bella wig.
你再用你的魔力之手帮我化妆
You work your magic with your magic make-up hands.
我们能处理好的
We'll figure something out.
好了
Okay. Oh.
等一下  好了
Wait. Okay.
-你要梳下头吗  -不用了  就这样
- Do you need a brush? - Oh, no, that's okay.
天呐
Oh, God.
好了
Okay.
给你
Here.
-看起来不错  -好的
- You look good. - Okay.
好的
Okay.
谢天谢地  我以为你忘了
Oh, thank God. I thought you forgot.
不  我  只是花了点时间打扮得性感一点
No, I, uh... It just takes a little time to look this hot.
对不起
Sorry.
我拿到了你要的那些零件
I got those parts that you asked for.
-我不知道  -哇哦
- I don't know-- - Oh, wow.
太棒了
That's amazing.
我没想到你这么快就弄到这些零件了
I'm surprised you got these parts so quickly.
算是当明星的好处吧
Yeah, well, the perks of being a pop star.
-肯定很爽  -也不完全是
- Must be nice. - Not really.
没有人有义务聆听明星的烦恼
But nobody should have to listen to pop star problems.
比如说想要什么就有什么
Like getting everything you could want,
包括很棒的车零件
including awesome bike parts?
不完全是这样
Not exactly.
或者说
Or, like, um...
也许不能遵从你的心声
not being able to follow your heart, maybe.
我听过你为音乐剧写的那些歌
I heard those songs that you wrote for the musical.
真的很不错
They're really good.
非常动听
Beautiful.
真的
Really?
不是开玩笑
Honestly?
是真的
Honestly.
那才是真正的你  对吧
That's the real you, right?
弗雷迪觉得我应该继续走现在的风格
Well, Freddie just thinks I need to stick to my brand
直到我的事业达到另一个高度
until my career reaches the next level.
然后我就可以做自己想做的了
Then I can do whatever I want.
也许弗雷迪错了
Freddie could be wrong.
嗯  只是他从来都是对的
Yes, it's just that he's been right about everything else.
就像我说的  明星的烦恼
Mm. Like I said, pop star problems.
我会帮你保密的
Well, they're safe with me.
嗯  我相信你
Yeah, I believe they are.
-你会需要这个的  -是的
-Yeah, you're gonna need that. - Yeah.
快来
Come on!
你能快速拧紧这些螺栓
Will you just tighten these bolts really quick
并且把传送带安好
and, um, finish putting on the belt.
我  我马上就回来
And I will be-- I'll be right back.
我得去检查一些东西
I've gotta go check on some things.
你会回来吗  你不在我可搞不定
You're gonna come back? I can't do this without you.
当然啦  我会回来的
Yes. Of course, I'll be back.
天呐
Oh, God.
-贝拉  -好了
- Bella... - There you go.
这里应该有你的声音
You're supposed to make a noise there.
我有错过试穿水晶鞋吗
Am I too late to try on the slipper?
王国中的每位少女都有机会
Every maiden in the land is granted the opportunity.
会是她吗
Could that be her?
让我等了一辈子的姑娘  来吧
The lass that I have waited my whole life for? Come!
快过来
Come!
请伸出你的脚
Please, present your foot.
怎么了
What?
你的痣换了一边
Your mole switched cheeks.
哦  这
Oh, it's...
这是我们家族中的女性都会经历的事
It happens to all the Snow women.
我们  呃  我们不喜欢谈论这些
We just, ahem, we just don't like to talk about it.
好吧
Okay. Uh...
好了  把你的脚抬起来
Okay, yeah, bring your foot up.
很好  继续
Good. And...
非常适合
A perfect fit!
太好了  现在我们站起来  走到前面
Okay, and now we get up, we come up,
准备好转圈
and get ready for the spin.
终于找到你了  我的公主
I have found you, my princess!
你不用再穿这些破布了
And you shall never wear rags again!
到你了
Come on.
来  来  来
Come, come, come.
不用担心  你的仙女教母在这里
Never fear, your fairy godmother is here.
让别人看到真实的你吧
Let others see you as I do.
转圈
Twirl.
-转圈  -赶紧的
- Twirl. - Come on.
像我教你那样轻甩手腕
Flick the wrist, like I showed you--
转圈
Twirl!
苍天啊  各位  快救火  拜托了
For cryin' out loud, people! Aah! Fix this! Please!
我们从头再来一次
And let's take it from the top.
贝拉
Bella...
她去哪儿了
Now where is she?
你画错痣的位置了
So you put the mole in the wrong s--
乔吉
Georgie?
好吧  我自己来
Okay. Here we go.
乔吉  你  你在这干嘛
Georgie, what are-- What are you doing here?
泰莎
Well, Tessa...
里德在找你  我就看下自己能不能帮上忙
Reed was looking for you so I offered to help.
好吧  好吧
Um, right, right.
我会
I will, um...
我  泰莎  接下来的事就交给我吧
I, Tessa, will take it from here.
-多谢了  乔吉  -不客气
- Thank you, Georgie. - You're welcome.
抱歉了
Sorry. Oh.
还好吧  你脸看上去很红
Are you okay? You look a little bit flushed.
我没事
It's ok
没事就好
Ah, you're okay.
你们看到贝拉了吗  她不见了
Have you seen Bella? She's AWOL.
没看到
Uh, no.
她会回来的  她答应过我不会再失踪的
No, she'll be back. She promised not to disappear again.
是啊  承诺有啥用
Yeah, right. So much for promises.
我想说什么来着
Um, where was I? Oh...
你知道吗  我
You know what, I--
我刚刚好像看到贝拉了
I think I, uh, I just saw Bella,
我还是去确认一下
And I think I should probably just go check on her
不要啊  别走
No, don't go,
拜托了  我马上要去排练了
please. I've got to go and perform in a minute.
就一会儿  我马上就回来
Um, this will just take a second. I'll be right back.
可让我找到你了
There you are!
迪万  嗨
Divine! Hi!
我知道你想干嘛
Oh, I know what you were doing.
-是吗  -当然
- You do?  - Yes.
这双眼睛看透了一切
These eyes see everything.
是吗
You do.
我知道你幻想着自己
Ooh, I know you have your own little fantasies
能够站在舞台上  但是
about being up on stage, but, heh,
偷偷溜进灰姑娘的贵宾休息室
lurking around the VIP area of Cinderella is just...
也太可悲了  坦白说  有点吓人
sad, and frankly, a little creepy.
的确是  你说的对  我很抱歉
Right. Yeah. Of course. Um, I'm so sorry.
-我明白了  不会再这样了  -那就好
- No more creeping. Understood. - Oh, good.
礼服在哪里
Now, where are those gowns?
-礼服  -哦  礼服
- The gowns! - Oh, the gowns!
-礼服在哪里  -礼服  其实
- Where are the gowns? - The gowns. I was about
我正要去拿礼服
to pick the gowns up, actually.
你也可以一起来  不过
You could come with, unless, of course,
你不想被人看到你在服务区吧
you don't wanna be seen in, you know, the service area.
五分钟内送到套房来
Have them in the suite in five minutes.
你得帮我们穿好
You need to help us get dressed.
好的  我知道了
Yes, of course, heh.
对不起  我来晚了  我得找更多联系人
Sorry I'm late. I had to find more contacts.
-没关系  -快结束了吗
- It's okay. - Is this almost over?
还没  现在我必须同时出现在三个地方了
No. Now I need to be in three places at once.
这就是我所说的明星魅力
Now that's what I call star power.
转起来  姑娘们  散发你们的魅力
Twirl, girls, twirl for Sparkles.
对了  泰莎
Oh, Tessa.
我有东西给你
I have something for you.
-给我的  -我怎么会忘记你呢  泰莎
- For me? - I didn't forget you, Tessa.
拿去吧
There you go.
没有服装要怎么参加化装舞会呢
You can't go to a costume ball without a costume.
谢谢你  迪万
Wow. Thank you, Divine.
你太客气了
You're so welcome.
哦  我们会给他们  哦  我们会给他们
Oh, we gonna give 'em Oh, we gonna give 'em
我们会给他们
We gonna give 'em
可以谈论的话题
S-somethin' somethin' Somethin' to talk about
我们会给他们  哦  我们会给他们
We gonna give 'em Oh, we gonna give 'em
哦  我们会给他们  哦  我们会给他们
Oh, we gonna give 'em Oh, we gonna give 'em
可以谈论的话题
S-somethin' somethin' Somethin' to talk about
穿着古驰和普拉达走进大门
Walk in the door Rockin' Gucci and that Prada
男孩们想要大声呐喊
Your homeboys They tryin' to holler...
好了  姑娘们  准备好光彩夺目吧
All right, girls. Let the dazzling begin.
挺直身子  微笑
Stand up straight. Smile.
抬头挺胸
Chest forward.
别挡我路  大家伙  哈哈哈
Outta my way, big baby! Ha-ha-ha!
我们会给他们
And we gonna give 'em
这里有很多灰姑娘
Oh, there's a lot of Cinderellas here.
姑娘们  站我后面
You girls, in the back.
勇敢点  奥林匹亚
Gallantry, Olympia
大家好
Hello.
我谨代表哈尔斯顿和皇家泻湖度假酒店
On behalf of the Halstons and Royal Lagoons Resorts,
欢迎各位来到贵宾化妆舞会
welcome to the VIP Costume Ball!
首先  有个小问题
First, one little question.
有人准备好放松了吗
Is anyone in this room ready to get loose?
好了  音乐响起来
Okay. Play the music.
我看见你在凝视这里
I see you there Staring here
舞动起来  你在害怕什么
Make a move Why are you scared?
忘记时间  尽情放纵自我
Push yourself Forget the clock
醒来以前  仍有大把时光
We got all night Then still wake up
散下秀发   只为今晚狂欢
Let down your hair For just one night
来吧  你在害羞什么
Come on, now Why are you still shy?
我看见你在凝视这里
I see you there Staring here
舞动起来
Make a move
动起来  宝贝  放松  放松
Come on, baby Get loose, loose
忘掉烦恼
Let it go
放松  在舞池里放纵自我
Get loose, loose On the floor
放松  尽情享受人生乐趣
Get loose, loose Have some fun
夜色才刚刚降临
The night has just begun
动起来  宝贝  放松  放松
Come on, baby Get loose, loose
忘掉烦恼
Let it go
放松  在舞池里放纵自我
Get loose, loose On the floor
放松  尽情享受人生乐趣
Get loose, loose Have some fun
好有趣的装扮
Interesting choice of costume.
我是只企鹅
I'm a penguin.
是  我看出来了
Yes, you are.
你能溜走吗
Can you sneak away?
这样我们就能把车修好了
Uh, so we can, uh, finish the bike.
我会找个机会溜出去的
I'll waddle out somehow.
泰莎
Tessa?
-怎么了  -我头发掉了
- Yeah? - My hair broke.
你得帮我把它接回去
You have to help me put it back together.
给我五分钟
Five minutes.
你和你那个神秘女孩怎么样了
How's your mystery girl working out for you?
她是个天才  但是有点古怪
She's talented but she's flaky.
她肯定有自己的原因
Oh, I'm sure she has her reasons.
是啊
Yeah.
可能我更喜欢我能信任的人吧
Maybe I'd just prefer someone I can trust.
她有趣
Someone who's funny.
喜欢笑
Likes to laugh.
也很聪明
Smart, of course.
身手还很敏捷
Smartenly probably.
超级可爱
Who's amazingly cute.
走起路来摇摇晃晃的
And waddles.
我觉得车没问题了
I think that should do it.
你想骑上去试试吗
You wanna try and start her up?
不用了  你来吧
No, you take the honors.
你修好了
You did it!
我们修好了  我们成功了
We did it. We totally did it.
那哈珀怎么办
What about Harper?
你在这儿呢
There you are!
你现在应该和豪斯顿家族会面
You're supposed to be meeting with the Halstons right now.
没错
Uh? Oh, yeah.
我忘记时间了
Um, I lost track of time.
能等我一分钟吗
Can you give me one minute?
你需要一分钟啊
Oh, you need a minute?
当然可以  当然  慢慢
By all means, yeah, take all the--
不行  一分钟也不行
No, you can't have a minute!
我们不能让金主等着  里德
We don't keep the big money waiting, Reed.
我过会儿给你打电话
I'll call you later.
快走  快走
Let's go. Let's go.
弗雷迪
Freddie?
那个  豪斯顿家族
The-- The Halstons...
哈珀也会来吗
Um, will Harper be there?
会  她要飞过来  给里德一个惊喜
Yes, she's flying out to surprise Reed.
我安排的
I arranged it.
所以他们  他们在一起了
So they're-- They're together.
泰莎
Oh, Tessa.
我知道待在里德这样的男孩子身边的时间肯定很短暂
I know it must be a rush being around a guy like Reed.
我是说  他马上就要成为巨星了
I mean, he's about to become a huge star--
这个我一点都不在乎
I couldn't care less about that.
哈珀才是合适他的人
--which is exactly why Harper is so right for him.
听着  我不知道里德跟你说了什么
Look, I don't know what Reed told you,
但是我确信他月底就要求婚了
but I'm pretty sure he's gonna propose by the end of the month.
什么
What?
很抱歉  泰莎  真的抱歉
I'm sorry, Tessa. Really.
对不起
I'm sorry.
我怎么这么傻
How could I have been so stupid?
结束了  我不演了
Well, I'm done. I'm done with the show.
我和里德也算完了  也和贝拉·斯诺彻底说再见
I'm done with Reed. Definitely done with Bella Snow.
演出不能没有贝拉
The show can't go on without Bella.
他很聪明  能想到办法的
He's resourceful. He'll figure something out.
说曹操曹操到
Unh. Speaking of...
听着  事情的关键在你自己
Look, this is about you.
你假冒贝拉·斯诺  就是为了一个男孩子吗
Did you become Bella Snow to win a boy?
不  不是  我假冒贝拉是因为我
No. No, I became Bella Snow because I was--
你在追逐自己的梦想
You were following your dream.
弗雷迪点醒了我  乔吉
Freddie was a real wake-up call, Georgie.
我什么都不是  也就会自欺欺人而已
I'm nobody. With just enough talent to delude myself.
泰莎  你自己决定
Oh, Tessa, it's your decision.
但是你要是现在放弃了  直到你死的那一天
But if you give up now, you'll always wonder,
你都会想  我要是没放弃会怎样呢
to your dying day, what if?
天啊  我好想你
God, I miss you.
你要是在这儿就好了  爸爸
I wish you were here, Dad.
也不一定是指在这儿
Well, not exactly here.
你要是我  会怎么做
What would you do if you were me?
我是这样一个人
I've never been one
不曾踏出自己的舒适圈
To step out Of my comfort zone
每次努力时  都担心自己止步不前
Whenever I try I'm afraid to just let go
我不知道我为什么逃跑
Don't know why I run
我不知道我为什么隐藏
Don't know why I hide
不让他人知晓自己真实的内心
Never let them know What I feel inside
我不知道我为什么恐惧
Don't know why I'm scared
当我站立于此
Just to take a chance
只能放手一搏
While I'm still standing here
我是这样一个人
I've never been one
不曾挣脱束缚自由翱翔
To break free
因为我总是在意他人的目光
'Cause I've always cared What everyone thinks of me
我不知道我为什么逃跑
Don't know why I run
我不知道我为什么隐藏
Don't know why I hide
不让他人知晓自己真实的内心
Never let them know What I feel inside
我不想放弃  我不想逃走
I don't want to settle Don't want to run
这里不是我的归宿
This is not Where I belong
演得很好
Well done.
就是  我知道自己的白马王子爱上别人之后
It's just-- It's hard to be Cinderella when I know
再演灰姑娘就太难了
my prince charming is in love with someone else.
冷静点  先把演出搞定
Get a grip. And focus on what's important.
你说得对
Yeah, you're right.
上台  让他们看看真正的你
Go back out there and show 'em who are you.
-好吗  -好
-Okay？ - Okay.
走吧
Let's go.
你明白现在的状况吗
Do you get what's going on?
不明白
No.
这就对了  我们就是刻薄
That's right. We're mean.
我们不喜欢你  就得给你来硬的
We don't like you. You're a hardball.
小莎  我在你房间等你  情况紧急  -乔
乔吉
Georgie?
乔
Georg--
迪万
Divine.
你好呀  "贝拉"
Cheerio, "Bella."
我就知道  你身上是饼干的味道
I knew you smelled like cookies.
你觉得你能逃得掉吗
Did you really think you could get away with this?
雅典娜身上流淌着成为明星的血液
Athena has the blood of a star running through her veins,
她一定会得到她应有的角色
and she will take her rightful place.
迪万  求求你别这样
Divine, please don't do this.
"求求你别这样  迪万"
"Please don't do this, Divine."
迪万  别  别  别这样
Divine, no. No, no, no, no.
别这样  迪万  求你了
No, Divine, please!
迪万
Divine!
有人听得见吗
Please, can someone hear me?
快点  想办法  泰莎  快想
Come on, think, Tessa, think.
乔吉  泰莎还好吗
Georgie, is Tessa all right?
她不接我电话  也不回我短信
She's not answering my calls or texts.
你要是真在乎她  为什么不问弗雷迪
If you really care, why don't you ask Freddie?
她就是我的命中注定
She's the one.
但是王子  我们怎么才能找到她
But how do we find her, my prince?
我们要找遍整个王国
We must search the land
找到那位能穿下这只水晶鞋的少女
to find the lovely maiden whose delicate foot fits this glass slipper.
我知道人们会说
I know they say
有时候一个尺寸人人适合
That sometimes That one size fits all
但是这里只有一位姑娘
But there's Only one girl in here
能够在舞会上艳压群芳
That's fit to be The belle of the ball
只有一位姑娘
There can only be one
在清晨的钟声敲响之前
So I'm looking for The right one
我要找寻到那命定之人
Before the end Of the night, sir
我要所有姑娘都聚起来
I need every girl To gather around
收起左脚  伸出右脚
Put your left in the crown Stick out the right one
我只需要你们  自然而然地穿上
'Cause all I need is you To slip, slip on slide 'em on
时间所剩无几  快点吧
'Cause we don't really Have much time, come on
当十二点的钟声响起  那就为时已晚
When the clock hits 12 Major fail
三  二  一  好了  就现在
Three, two, one Okay, now
乌拉  呼啦  乌拉  呼啦
Eeny, meeny, miny, moe
我不确定  谁才是她
Which girl's the one Man, I don't know
乌拉  呼啦  乌拉  呼啦
Eeny, meeny, miny, moe
到底是谁  才穿得下
Who's got the foot That'll rock the sole
鞋若合脚  就快穿上
Well, if the shoe fits Then go put it on
快穿上
Go put it on
鞋若合脚  就快穿上
Well, if the shoe fits Then go put it on
快穿上
Go put it on
你知道的  鞋若合脚
Well, if the shoe fits you You know what to do
快穿上
Put it on
贝拉怎么没在候场
Why isn't Bella in position?
我不知道  我正等着给她换衣服
I don't know. I've been waiting to dress her in--
她的演出服去哪儿了
Where's her costume?
你怎么回事
What is wrong with you?
-你怎么这么胖  -衣服太小了
- Why are you so fat? - It's so small.
我来试试
Let me try.
奥林匹亚  帮我们盯着
Olympia, keep watch!
我为什么不能当灰姑娘
Why can't I be Cinderella?
因为奥林匹亚  你不够优秀
Because Olympia! You're just not good enough!
等一下  妈妈  谁来演我的角色
Wait, Mom. Who's going to play my part?
欢迎莅临蔽舍
Welcome to our humble home.
王子殿下要求房里
His highness requests the presence
所有女士都出来一下
of all the ladies of the house.
我的两个女儿和我
My two daughters and I are--
你姐姐呢  亲爱的
Where's your sister, dear?
谁在乎  可能她死了吧
Who cares? Maybe she's dead.
不对  我想起来了  她在房间里
No, I remember. She's in her room.
我真蠢  怎么把这忘了
Silly me. How could I forget?
我是说  她远在底特律
I meant she's far, far away in Detroit.
停  等等  等等
Wait! Hold on, hold on.
我在这儿呢  母亲
Here I am, Mother!
继续找  一定要找到贝拉
Just keep going! And find Bella!
在皇家水晶鞋试穿日去底特律  怎么可能
...Detroit, when it's Royal Try-on-a-Glass-Shoe Day?
明明有菲力牛排
Why waste your princely time on ground beef
还在碎牛肉上浪费什么时间呢
when you could have filet mignon?
别害怕  我不咬人
Don't be afraid. I don't bite.
可能  就这里那里随便摸摸吧
Well, maybe a little bit here and there.
其实  我只是喜欢拥抱别人
Actually, I'm just all cuddles.
快点  问我妹妹
Go ahead, ask my sister.
恐怕我没法问这个问题了
That doesn't appear to be an option.
什么
Huh?
外边怎么了
What is happening out there?
我会让母亲知道  我足够优秀
I'll show Mom I'm good enough!
别拽了
Stop it!
你把一切都毁了
You're ruining everything!
你个坏姑娘  滚过来
Aah, you evil girl, come back here!
唉  鞋不合脚
Alas, it does not fit.
你确定吗  王子
Are you sure, Prince?
非常  非常确定
Really, really sure.
那就塞进去
Cram it in.
我不管  快去找人
Okay, I don't care, just do it.
不好意思  我要去喂马了
Uh, excuse me, I must go feed the horses.
哈喽  小家伙
Hello, guy.
我现在遇到点麻烦
Okay. So I'm kind of in a situation right now.
甜心  你能告诉我走哪条路吗
And you gotta tell me which way to go, sugar,
那边还是这边
that way or this way?
好了  走吧
Oh, okay. Here we go.
不行  我不在乎  演出不能叫停
No, I don't care. We're not gonna stop the show.
去  快去
Just do it, do it!
你干什么呢  你得去舞台上
What are you doing? I need you out there!
你先告诉我  你和泰莎说什么了
First tell me what you said to Tessa.
泰莎  里德  演出都一团糟了
Tessa? Reed, the show's a mess.
我找不到贝拉  她们干嘛呢
I can't find Bella-- What are they doing?
-我不知道  也不在乎  -这很重要
- I don't know and I don't care. - This is important.
你在哪儿呢呀  宝贝王子
Where you are, Prince dear.
你给我出来  不然我就砍了你
Get out here or I will cut you!
你跟她说什么了  告诉我
What did you say to her? Just tell me.
出  去
Go! Out!
不好
Oh, no.
别  别  别  别
No, no, no, no.
好了  如果房内没有其他女士
Right, if there are no other ladies in the house,
我们就该走了
then we must take our leave.
除非  听  你听见什么声音了吗
Unless, hark, do you hear something?
也许吧
Um, maybe?
我很肯定  我听到什么了
I'm sure I must have heard a noise!
真要这样么
Ow. Ow. Really?
我有错过试穿水晶鞋吗
Am I too late to try on the slipper?
哈喽  我有错过试穿
Oh, hello. Am I too late to try on--
我有错过试穿水晶鞋吗
Am I too late to try on the slipper?
我的天呐  你发什么疯
Oh, my God! What has gotten in to you?
停下  不行
Stop it, no!
我不会上台了
I'm not going back out there
除非你告诉我  你和泰莎说了什么
until you tell me what you said to Tessa.
不行
No!
好吧  我是说了点
Okay. I may have said something
你和哈珀订婚的事儿
about you and Harper getting engaged.
-就这样  -为什么  弗雷迪
- That's all. - Why, Freddie?
-你为什么和泰莎说那些  -你们  把麦遮住
- Why would you say that to Tessa? - Guys, cover your mic.
注意了  各位  敬请欣赏新版《灰姑娘》
Hold on, everybody, get ready for the new Cinderella.
你马上就要成为巨星了
You're on the verge of stardom.
里德  我都是为了你啊
Reed, I did it for you.
我知道你是好心  弗雷迪
I know you mean well, Freddie,
但是轮不到你为我做决定
but you do not get to make those calls for me.
哈珀就是我的朋友  我对她不是那种喜欢
Harper's just a friend, I don't like her that way.
不行
No!
泰莎  她挺好的  但是那有什么大不了的
Tessa, I mean, she's sweet, but what's the big deal?
重要的是  人生中第一次
The big deal is, for the first time in my life,
我坠入爱河了
I think I'm in love!
没有人愿意孤身一人
Nobody ever wants To be alone
因为我们都想要一个知心好友
'Cause we all want A friend to call our own
贝拉
Bella?
我有错过试穿水晶鞋吗
Am I too late to try on the slipper?
泰莎
Tessa?
你是灰姑娘
You're Cinderella?
抱歉  没有告诉你我的真实身份
I'm sorry I didn't tell you who I really was.
我从没想过像你这样的王子
I never thought that a prince like you
会爱上我这样的女孩
could ever love girl like me.
我更抱歉  让你受了苦
Not as sorry as I am, to have caused you any pain.
我的参谋  弗雷德里科  没有告诉我
My advisor, Frederico spoke not the truth
有关婚礼的实情
of my impending nuptials.
弗雷迪说我要和哈珀订婚的事  是假的
Freddie totally lied about me getting married to Harper.
我听到了
I heard.
在这个王国  声音能传很远
Sound travels quite well in this kingdom.
请来试试水晶鞋吧
Please, try on the glass slipper.
乐意之至
I'd love to.
你知道吗  我不需要一只鞋来告诉我
You know what? I don't need a shoe to tell me
我内心的感觉
what I really feel in my heart.
你就是我的命中注定
You're the one.
别拍了
Stop it!
别拍了  你恶心死了
Stop it, you're disgusting.
不要害怕  你的仙女教母已经到来
Never fear, your fairy godmother is here.
让世界看到真实的你吧
Let the world see you as I do.
转圈
Twirl.
太好了
Yes! Come on.
你的仙女教母做得很好
Your fairy godmother does great work.
那是当然
She really does.
我是这样一个人
I've never been one
不曾踏出自己的舒适圈
To step out Of my comfort zone
每次努力时  都担心自己止步不前
Whenever I try I'm afraid to just let go
我不知道我为什么逃跑
Don't know why I run
我不知道我为什么隐藏
Don't know why I hide
不让他人知晓自己真实的内心
Never let them know What I feel inside
我不想放弃  我不想逃走
I don't want to settle Don't want to run
这里
This is not
不是我的归宿
Where I belong
如同飞鸟  我注定飞翔
Like a bird I need to fly
张开双翼  寻找生命的意义
Spread my wings And find my life
如同飞鸟  我飞入高空
Like a bird I'm up so high
飞出牢笼  是时候大放异彩
Out of the cage It's my time to shine
是时候大放异彩
It's my time to shine
如同飞鸟  我自由飞翔
Like a bird I'm free to fly
所以告诉我  告诉我  我为什么要逃避
So tell me, tell me Why don't I?
如同飞鸟  我自由飞翔
Like a bird Free to fly
张开双翼  寻找生命的意义
Spread my wings Find my life
如同飞鸟  我飞入高空
Like a bird Up so high
飞出牢笼  是时候大放异彩
Out the cage It's time to shine
张开双翼  寻找生命的意义
Spread my wings Find my life
如同飞鸟  我飞入高空
Like a bird Up so high
飞出牢笼  是时候大放异彩
Out the cage It's time to shine
如同飞鸟  我飞入高空
Like a bird Up so high
飞出牢笼  是时候大放异彩
Out the cage It's time to shine
给我打电话
Call me.
谢谢你
Thank you.
表演太棒了
That was incredible.
我太为你骄傲了
I'm so proud of you.
乔吉  我不知道怎么才能谢你
Georgie, I don't know how to thank you.
用不着
You don't have to.
也许你需要这个
I thought you might need this.
你最好了  没有你我该怎么办
You're the best. What would I do without you?
抱歉  兄弟  我搞砸了
Sorry, buddy. I messed up.
如果你不想让我当你的经纪人了
But if you don't want me to be your manager anymore,
我也能理解的
I'll understand.
不  我当然需要了
No, of course I do.
另外  也许你甚至还有机会
Plus, you may even get the chance
和一位有才华的新星一起工作呢
to work with a talented new star.
嘿  帅哥  我们走吧
Hey, charming, let's bounce.
寻找生命的意义
Found my life
宝贝  我们做到了
Sweety, we did it.
我知道我不能独占所有功劳  但是
I know I can't take all the credit, but...
要是没有我  也不会这么成功不是吗
it certainly wouldn't have happened without me, right?
迪万  你是所有女孩心中
Divine, you've been the best evil stepmother
恶毒后妈的典范
a girl could ever ask for, but, uh--
谢谢你
Thank you.
我们是时候分道扬镳了
I think it's definitely time for us to part ways.
记得给我打电话
Call me.
所以  你想去哪儿
So? Where do you wanna go?
大放异彩
Time to shine...
哪里都想去
Everywhere.
从某方面来看  我们都会遇到一个激动人心的机会
At some point, we all come across an exciting opportunity,
但是我们可能对新的旅途产生畏惧  我的建议呢
a new path that might scare us. My advice?
踩离合器  即刻出发
Pop the clutch, hit the road
努力过上幸福美满的生活
and make your happily-ever-after come true.
迪幻
Deefun
■
扫描右侧二维码
关注迪幻微信公众号
获取青春影视资讯趣闻
字幕组长期招募中
报名请发送邮件到
deefunbbs@gmail.com
整日忙碌  却一无所获
Working all day Don't do a thing
其实你坐在驾驶座  可以掌控自己的生活
Life's what you make it You're in the driver's seat
加大油门  拧动点火
Rev your engine Crank the ignition
给我钥匙  你怎样都无法阻止我
Give me the key Don't need your permission
妈妈总是说
Mama always told me
生活中没什么好怕的
There's nothing In this life to fear
从懵懵懂懂到无所不能  你将会想念现在的我
You're gonna miss me Zero to sixty
把生活拉回正轨
Kicking it into gear
是我坐在驾驶座  掌控着生活
I'm in control I'm behind the wheel
想去哪里  就将一往无前
And I'm gonna steer Where I wanna steer
是我坐在驾驶座  掌控着生活
I'm in control I'm behind the wheel
想去哪里  就将一往无前
And I'm gonna steer Where I'm gonna steer
加足马力
Go full throttle
活着
Living
活着  活着
Living, living
没什么好怕的
Nothing to fear
让自己走上正轨
Put yourself in gear
加足马力
Go full throttle
我知道大雨即将落下
I know that rain Is falling
不必满面愁容
Don't look So sad about it
我知道也许会有点痛
I know It hurts a little
你想要高声呼喊
You wanna Scream and shout
我有挽救方法
I got the remedy
就跟着节奏一遍一遍尽情摇摆
Just let the rhythm Take you over and over
一遍又一遍
Over and over
我知道你万分沮丧
I know you're down
我来让你展开笑颜
Let me pick you up
我知道你很坚强
I know you're strong
我知道你很坚韧
I know you're tough
你想坐在一旁
You wanna sit
但你需要舞动
You need to move
感受音乐  让我来为你示范
Let me show you how to do it Feel the music
如果你开心  那就鼓掌
Hey, you gotta clap When you're happy
如果你难过 也要鼓掌
Clap when you're sad
无论开心难过  都要鼓掌
Clap when your day is good Or when it's going bad
不要顾虑太多
Don't think too much About it
学会放空自我
Just keep your head In the sky
说"嘿"的感觉是不是妙不可言
Now don't it feel good To say, "Hey"
如果你开心  那就鼓掌
Clap when you're happy
如果你难过 也要鼓掌
Clap when you're sad
无论开心难过  都要鼓掌
Clap when your day is good Or when it's going bad
不要顾虑太多
Don't think too much About it
学会放空自我
Just keep your head In the sky
说"嘿"的感觉是不是妙不可言
Now don't it feel good To say, "Hey"
我已找到解开困惑的新途径
I got a new solution To all of this confusion
你会庆幸你加入其中
You'll feel so glad You made it
不要让事情变得复杂
Don't make it Complicated
这是崭新的一天
This is a brand new day
就跟着音乐一遍一遍尽情摇摆
Just let the music Take you over and over
一遍又一遍
Over and over
我知道你万分沮丧
I know you're down
我来让你展开笑颜
Let me pick you up
我知道你很坚强
I know you're strong
我知道你很坚韧
I know you're tough
你想坐在一旁
You wanna sit
但你需要舞动
You need to move
感受音乐  让我来为你示范
Let me show you how to do it Feel the music
如果你开心  那就鼓掌
Hey, you gotta clap When you're happy
如果你难过  也要鼓掌
Clap when you're sad
无论开心难过  都要鼓掌
Clap when your day is good Or when it's going bad
不要顾虑太多
Don't think too much About it
学会放空自我
Just keep your head In the sky
说"嘿"的感觉是不是妙不可言
Now don't it feel good To say, "Hey"
如果你开心  那就鼓掌
Clap when you're happy
如果你难过  也要鼓掌
Clap when you're sad
无论开心难过  都要鼓掌
Clap when your day is good Or when it's going bad
不要顾虑太多
Don't think too much About it
学会放空自我
Just keep your head In the sky
说"嘿"的感觉是不是妙不可言
Now don't it feel good To say, "Hey"
如果你开心  那就鼓掌
Clap when you're happy
如果你难过  也要鼓掌
Clap when you're sad
无论开心难过  都要鼓掌
Clap when your day is good Or when it's going bad
不要顾虑太多
Don't think too much About it
学会放空自我
Just keep your head In the sky
这感觉是不是妙不可言
Now don't it feel good To say...
嘿  嘿  嘿
Hey, hey, hey
哈哈  抱歉
Ha, sorry.